the future pulling us forwards an
attractor point in the future
ever increasing ball of gravity multiple
paths and at the end of each of these
paths a new cause of future forming
itself accreting matter around it all
the intentions of the world trying to
shape a new future and we battling with
all these different forces or
synergizing with all these different
forces to select which is going to be
our individual and collective future
throwing our intention from the present
like an arrow aiming for an invisible
target with time our arrow becoming
sharper and sharper piercing deeper and
deeper into space-time until we can hit
the future we want pulling me towards it
asking me what is it that I want to do
what is it that I want I do not know the
answer yet I pretend that I do so I try
to force my will on agency and I tried
to play a character that I know I'm not
prepared for so I seek many many many
many many ways many many many many parts
to fill that character all these little
games that I learn for myself
all these little ordeals and put myself
through all so that I can be worthy of
them fool why why do I do it
the future is calling the future is
calling a great question to which we do
not know the answer to try and find some
water inside of the chaos we try an
answer on to the future we try to find a
role we're trying to find a mask that we
can play inside of that will interact
with the world in a way that will
generate some kind of predictability
some kind of future that we can touch
that is tangible and yet the future we
need is not in the future it is in the
present fully paid attention to the
present gives birth to the future we
must become mid White's to the future
inside of the present moment why is it
my boss seemed to care so then why is it
my burden to bear
why cannot i let go of this column and
choose to be right now in this moment
not asking of it anything not seeking of
it anything not pushing not pulling or
just being why is it that I need to
worry about something and I have no
control over because I barely understand
what has happened and what is currently
happening so why am i reaching out with
my mind
am i reaching out with my heart what is
responding to this phone which part of
me do I even know I don't so why do I
think is the mask on my face is the mask
on my heart he where is what is it I do
not understand for that
a fully integrated response to the call
something is making the call the call is
a cry it's a scream of pain is being in
pain as being lost its unity in a
splintered humanity is humanity a
symptom of the splintering of
consciousness and needs to find its way
back to the unity is this the why is
this the call to bring all humans back
into unity to bring all of consciousness
back into unity through the medium of
the integrated human being or unity you
are so lonely if you are - you are an
opposition only if you are in three are
you actually in relation this is
something I learned recently fully if
you are in three are you actually in
relation so it's a clearly unity that I
require that I seek that I call out for
or is it really just connection is it
connection then I'm really looking for
what is unity if it is lonely if all of
us went in one there is the fun in that
how am i able to be okay with you being
different and yet in that diversity
heralding our unity how do I see unity I
see it in multiplicity the capacity to
be different there I see that the power
of unity lies
unity connected to duality duality
connected to unity the Trinity only one
but also to and thus three Lila playing
with duality knowing that behind all the
masks behind the hide-and-seek there is
the unity practicing unity in practicing
duality returning to the oneness when
necessary seeing the difference in
embracing it when necessary the ecology
of practices of unity and jus ality
which allow us to generate a future
where these opposites coincide side by
side when the singular appears
differently to each of the different
parts of the whole Lila where the
individual or the singular appears
differently to each of the different
parts of the code interesting what do
you think for it suits and it changes
and involves and it melts to suit each
one of us to each one of us different
from each other we reconcile what we see
as that which allows us to be who we are
and to return to what that which we
already are or was first I do not
understand it makes no sense to me
because somewhere there is a pull and a
push at the same time and in that I
don't know which way to go so I realized
maybe just fallen pushed by the void
pushing us forwards whence we came and
pulling us to well we must go back to
the void
avoid inside of everyone something which
makes us all the same different shapes
of the void within everyone giving
different forms to our consciousness to
our needs to our wills to our desires
what part of us needs to be filled the
interconnection of people with opposing
voids void meeting void complementing
each other
avoid pulling us into the future in
order for warrington there needs to
exist contrast it is contrast that I
truly truly truly admire his bag of meat
and bones its capacity to direct and
wield consciousness is all because that
creates divine power which is contrast
if it not where for contrast I would
never be able to know the difference
with that which I call light and that
which I called up to me if there is a
cord to mean if there is a source it is
one that is capable of contrast because
anything that is individual does not
allow me to experience myself so for me
to experience myself the only thing that
allows it is contrast so there's the
cord and I
[Music]